# **DUSTIN MOONEY**

202.525.6550 | DUSTIN@MOONEY.ME | LINKEDIN.COM/IN/DUSTINMOONEY

#### EDUCATION

**B.A. POLITICAL SCIENCE** 

*University of Central Florida* 2013

# KEY SKILLS

Project Management, Marketing, Client Services, Software as a Service, SaaS, Client Success, Client Experience, Windows, Microsoft Office Suite, Apple OS, Google Workplace, Chrome OS, Linux, Adobe CC, Salesforce CRM, SquareSpace, HTML, CSS, SEO, SEM, WordPress, HubSpot

# CERTIFICATIONS

Advanced Google Analytics

Google Ads

AdMall

**Analytical Forecasting** 

# ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### CONSULTANT

REBUILD Globally 2015-2018 - Remote / Haiti

#### **CAMPAIGN STAFFER**

U.S. Senate Campaign 2015-2016 - Remote

#### AID WORKER

International Volunteer HQ 2013-2014 - Nairobi, Kenya

REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST

## SUMMARY

Strategic business and customer success leader with strengths in project management, client relations, client experience, branding, and client strategy. Leverage relationships to drive outcomes for clients and key stakeholders. *Core Competencies Include:* 

Management | Customer Success | Project Management | Communications

# EXPERIENCE

#### CUSTOMER SUCCESS MANAGER, PUBLIC SECTOR

PublicInput / Remote / 2021 - Present

Work with a team of highly experienced Client Success Managers in the public sector to achieve public engagement goals and objectives. Manage a portfolio of local government sector clients to gauge the public interest on specific projects.

- Leverage insights from proprietary public engagement SaaS platform to inform government clients on community engagement outcomes. Used insights to drive cross-selling opportunities.
- **Maintained a 96%** *retention rate* **year-over-year** by managing client relationships from onboarding through renewal. Provide strategies to leverage platform to increase public engagement and usage to ensure retention.

#### **CLIENT SUCCESS MANAGER**

Client Savvy / Raleigh, NC & Remote / 2019 - 2021

Work with a team of highly skilled Client Experience (CX) professionals to achieve marketing and client success objectives. Executed a variety of marketing campaigns. Maintained relations with executives to implement and execute their CX programs.

- **Generated a successful end-to-end marketing strategy.** Execution included website development, podcast production, social media, and content creation.
- Directed client experience and financial consulting that led to an 11% increase in revenue for Faith Technologies while diversifying their portfolio.

# MANAGER, CLIENT SUCCESS

The McClatchy Company / Raleigh, NC / 2017 - 2018

Led team of 13 Digital Strategists. Served as an intermediary between sales, production, and client success teams for this publicly traded publishing company for clients like UNC, Republic Wireless, and the Carolina Hurricanes, among others.

- Led team of Digital Strategists who managed client relationships focused on identifying needs, executing campaigns, and reporting success metrics.
- Migrated into multidisciplinary team with a 43% increase in recurring revenue as we integrated success, sales, ad-ops, and operations.

## ACCOUNT DIRECTOR / SENIOR ACCOUNT MANAGER / ACCOUNT MANAGER

IZEA Worldwide / Orlando, FL & Remote / 2010 - 2017

Assumed increasing levels of accountability for the leader of influencer and content marketing software (SaaS) and services to the world's leading agencies and brands. Managed relationships with Viacom, JPMorgan, US Army, CDC, and Johnson & Johnson.

- **Project managed \$7M+ annually** for marketing initiatives on behalf of brands, advocacy organizations, and government agencies.
- Generated new business of \$1.2M+ yearly from clients like NIH and others.